oemsecrets.com 2015-10-23

# OEMSecrets.com - Terms & Conditions

Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using OEMsecrets.com's services. The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use: 

## LIABILITY DISCLAIMER 

ANY SERVICES OR INFORMATION GAINED THAT IS PROVIDED BY OEM SECRECTS IS AT THE USERS OWN RISK. INACCURATE INFORMATION OR ERRORS IN THE SYSTEM MAY BE INCLUDED. OEM SECRETS IS ONLY PROVIDING INFORMATION AND PROVIDING A COMMUNIATION BETWEEN THE USER AND THE SUPPLIER HOLDING STOCK. OEM SECRETS DOES NOT REPRESENT THE SUPPLIERS LISTING STOCK ON THE WEBSITE. OEM SECRETS DOES NOT PROVIDE ANY FORM OF WARRANTY FOR PRODUCTS OR SERVICES OF SUPPLIER INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE SYSTEM. PURCHASE ORDERS MUST BE SENT TO THE SUPPLIERS DIRECTLY AFTER THE QUOTATION PERIOD. For suppliers applying, gaining membership and uploading inventory; and users browsing and using this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern OEMsecrets.com's relationship with you in relation to this website. The term 'OEMSecrets.com' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is OEMSECRETS.COM , UNIT 18 KATHRYN AVENUE, MONKS CROSS YORK YO32 9JS ENGLAND. Our holding company registration number is 05557276 . The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website. The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use: The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice. Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law. Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements. This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions. All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of, or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website. Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence. From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s). You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without OEMsecrets.com's prior written consent. Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of England, Scotland and Wales. 

## SECURITY

As a login is no longer required to list inventory on OEMsecrets.com, there is no sensitive information held on our servers with reference to our members. Any information provided to us by you is safeguarded on our secure servers at your discretion. You may contact us at anytime if you wish to have any information about you that OEMsecrets.com holds removed/or destroyed. 

## Charges

It is 100% FREE for users to search for electronic components on OEMsecrets.com, there are NO charges. Listing fees for INSTOCK inventory on OEMsecrets.com are negotiated at point of supplier's approval by OEMsecrets, any future changes to fees will be implemented 30 days prior to the renewal period/or otherwise stated on the website/or in these terms and conditions. All other advertisements on OEMsecrets.com are subject to advertisment placements/or term, any future changes to fees will be implemented 7 days prior to the renewal period/or otherwise stated on the website/or in these terms and conditions. 

## TERMINATION

OEMsecrets shall refund to you the fee paid for your subscription less a 20% cancellation charge should termination be requested by you within the first 30 days after receipt of payment. Any cancellation requested after this period (30 days) is non-refundable. OEMsecrets reserves the right to terminate an agreement should the terms and conditions of the contract be broken, which is non-refundable. OEMsecrets.com reserves the right to modify the Terms & Conditions to inform users of any future changes to fees, so please review it frequently. OEMSecrets.com is available in UK English only. 

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

WWW.OEMSECRETS.COM may link to other 3rd party websites. These sites are not under the remit of WWW.OEMSECRETS.COM and any content of these sites has no reflection of WWW.OEMSECRETS.COM and users are to enter these sites at their own risk. 

## PARAMETERS OF USE

All internet users may search for electronic components on OEMsecrets.com. It is at OEMsecrets.com discretion as to grant suppliers approval to list inventory on the website, suppliers that meet the criteria. Suppliers agree to list IN-STOCK inventory only on OEMsecrets.com. Suppliers agree to not include counterfeit components in their inventory feeds. Regular checks will be carried out to monitor and control this process. Failure to respond to quality control checks will see their membership revoked without notice. Any supplier providing false information to gain access to the site or any supplier who breaks the conditions of use may have their membership privileges revoked. OEMsecrets.com reserves the right to deny or approve any membership. There are no restrictions to the amount of searches a user can make on OEMsecrets.com. Use of the Site and system OEMsecrets.com is for internal sourcing use only. Information cannot be shared with 3rd parties. Search results are only providing information, quantities and stock confirmation are the responsibility of the supplier. 

## COMMUNICATIONS

OEMsecrets.com allows users to search for parts and request price and delivery from suppliers showing stock. This communication system is in place for ease of use. By using this communication service you agree that you will not; Use any form of profanity, abusive language, violate legal rights of others. Use any form of discriminative behaviour Use this communication service for any form of criminal activity Send any form of untrue or misleading information 

## PRIVACY POLICY

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. (1) What information do we collect? We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data: [(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including [your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views]);] [(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including [CONTACT NAME, POSITION, COMPANY NAME, TELEPHONE NUMBER, FAX NUMBER, EMAIL ADDRESS, WEBSITE ADDRESS, NATURE OF BUSINESS INFORMATION]);] [(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including [CONTACT NAME, POSITION, COMPANY NAME, TELEPHONE NUMBER, FAX NUMBER, EMAIL ADDRESS, WEBSITE ADDRESS, NATURE OF BUSINESS INFORMATION]);] [(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including [[CONTACT NAME, POSITION, COMPANY NAME, TELEPHONE NUMBER, FAX NUMBER, EMAIL ADDRESS, WEBSITE ADDRESS, NATURE OF BUSINESS INFORMATION]);] [(e) any other information that you choose to send to us; and]

**[(2) Cookies: A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We [may] use [both] ['session' cookies] [and 'persistent' cookies] on the website. [We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; .] [We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; .] We may use this information to enhance the service and user experience. [Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.] [Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.] [We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.]**

[Our [advertisers/payment services providers] may also send you cookies.] [We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin.] Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking 'Tools', 'Internet Options', 'Privacy', and selecting 'Block all cookies' using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites[ including OEMsecrets.com]. (3) Using your personal data Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website. We may use your personal information to: [(a) administer the website;] [(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;] [(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;] [(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;] [(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;] [(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;] [(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;] [(h) send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications) ;] Internal divisions may proactively contact you to help with specific problems or enquiries. [(i) provide internal divisions with statistical information about our users. [(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and] [Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.] [We may share your information internally with a division of the company however, We will not without your expressed consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.] [All our website financial transactions are handled through our holding company. ] (4) Disclosures We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy. In addition, we may disclose information about you: (a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law; (b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; (c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and [(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.] Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties. We will only provide information to our own holding company. (5) International data transfers Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy. Information which you provide may be transferred to countries [(including [the United States], Europe, Asia ])] which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Areas (EEA). [In addition, [personal information that you submit for publication on the website] will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.] [You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.] (6) Security of your personal data We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. [We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted .] Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. [You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.] (7) Policy amendments We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. [We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.] (8) Your rights You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00). You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes). (9) Third party websites The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. (10) Updating information Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. (11) Contact If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [support@oemsecrets.com] or by post to [OEMSecrets.com,18 Kathryn Avenue, Monks Cross, York, YO32 9JS. (12) Data controller The data controller responsible for our website is [OEMSECRETS LTD]. Our data protection registration number is [05557276].
